{"description":"A set of questions to test the software with","name":"Pilot AD 17 Oct","version":1,"questions":[{"question":"195. (Airdrop) Loading the GPS keys improves SKE performance","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"1C-17A-1, Para: 2-675 (N)","responses":["True","False"]},{"question":"196. (Airdrop) Maximum troop door opening airspeed is _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"1C-17A-1, Para: Table 5-11","responses":["280 KCAS\/Mach 0.62","350 KCAS\/Mach 0.825","310 KCAS\/Mach 0.74","250 KCAS\/Mach 0.62"]},{"question":"197. (Airdrop) If excessive crosstrack (greater than ______) is predicted at 15 seconds prior to the CARP\/HARP, the CAWS annunciates \"AUTO DROP,\" and the AUTO DROP annunciator on the instrument panel illuminates.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"1C-17A-1-4, Para: 1-10","responses":["100 yards","250 yards","300 yards","500 yards"]},{"question":"198. (Airdrop) Formation takeoff minimums are no lower than a ____ ceiling and ____ mile(s) visibility. Formation landing minimums are ____","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"AFMAN 11-2C17V3, Para: 15.3","responses":["500 ft; 1 mile; 300 ft ceiling and 3\/4 mile visibility","600 ft; 2 miles; 500 ft ceiling and 2 miles visibility","300 ft; 3\/4 mile; 600 ft ceiling and 2 miles visibility","200 ft 1\/2 mile; published minimums for the airport"]},{"question":"199. (Airdrop) Lead will announce unplanned airspeed changes of ____ knots or more.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFMAN 11-2C17V3, Para: 15.9.4.3","responses":["10","15","20","All airspeed changes must be announced"]},{"question":"200. (Airdrop) (Formation Holding Pattern, Holding Pattern in Lieu of Procedure Turn, or Procedure Turn Pattern) During formation recoveries lead","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"AFMAN 11-2C17V3, Para: 15.10.8.1","responses":["Will enter a minimum of 1,000 feet above procedure turn or GCA pickup altitude","Will not enter from the quadrant requiring a turn to the non-maneuvering side","Will not fly 45\/180 ground tracks","All of the above"]},{"question":"201. (Airdrop) Offset PIs are computed from the surveyed center PI. When used, a ___ yard left\/right offset will be used for 3-ship operations and a ___ yard left\/right offset will be used for 2-ship operations.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFI13-217, Para: 2.5.7.1","responses":["250; 125","500; 250","500; 125","250; 75"]},{"question":"202. (Airdrop) For jumpmaster-directed airdrops, the PF must establish drop altitude and airspeed early (normally __ minutes prior to green light). At approximately __ until scheduled drop time, the loadmaster permits the jumpmaster to begin spotting procedure","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3-3.C17, Para: 7.9.3","responses":["2; 2; 1","5; 3; 1","3; 3; 2","5; 2; 1"]},{"question":"203. (Airdrop) (Formation En Route Altitude Changes) For climbs and descents greater than 2,000 feet, use _____ FPM (or previous rate if lower).For 2,000 feet or less, use _____ FPM (or previous rate if lower).","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3-3.C17, Para: Table 8.4","responses":["2000; 1000","1000; 1000","2000; 1500","1000; 500"]},{"question":"204. (Airdrop) The minimum formation takeoff interval is ____ seconds","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFTTP 3-3.C17, Para: 8.8.4.1","responses":["20","30","40","60"]},{"question":"205. (Airdrop) For visual-in-trail formation slowdowns, the desired spacing is ____ feet between element leads (_____ feet between all aircraft).","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFTTP 3-3.C17, Para: Fig 8.31","responses":["12000; 4000","6000; 2000","12000; 2000","6000; 4000"]},{"question":"206. (Airdrop) (Visual Formation Airdrop) For drift angles of ____ degree(s), wingmen adjust their lateral formation position to maintain the same relative ground track as the element lead over the DZ, avoiding wake turbulence from the preceding aircraft.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3-3.C17, Para: 8.11.5.1.1","responses":["4 and greater","TRUE","2","3"]},{"question":"207. (Airdrop) (Personnel Formation Airdrop Escape) If required to move back to en route crosstrack, delay post drop maneuvering to en route visual or SKE XTRK position until end of usable DZ (MC Red Light) and \"load clear.\"","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3-3.C17, Para: 8.11.7.2","responses":["True","False"]},{"question":"208. (Airdrop) The Quick Drop Checklist may be used for:","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"1C-17A-1-4, Para: 2-98","responses":["A subsequent static line personnel airdrop when all troop doors are closed between passes","A subsequent heavy equipment airdrop pass","A subsequent CDS airdrop when the cargo door and ramp remain open between passes","All of the above"]},{"question":"209. (Airdrop) Block 18 - 19D. Airdrop with _____ selected on the MCD's NAV SENSORS-CONTROL PAGE will cause numerous\r\nUNABLE RNP messages to annunciate.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"1C-17A-1-4, Para: 2-118 step 8 (N)","responses":["MGPS","CGPS","SKE ZM","RADIO"]},{"question":"210. (Airdrop) During the airdrop slowdown checklist, the SED thrust rating is selected to MAX if:","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"1c-17A-1-4, Para: 2-119 Step 2","responses":["Flying in a wing position","Selecting 3\/4 or FULL flaps","Dropping heavy equipment platforms","Both B. and C."]},{"question":"211. (Airdrop) _____________, especially with less than _______ feet spacing between aircraft, will increase the likelihood of nuisance SKE GPS DENIED messages.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"1C-17A-1, Para: 1-2070","responses":["Unkeyed MGPS operation, 12,000","Unkeyed MGPS operation, 3000","Keyed MGPS operation, 6000","CGPS containment with Keyed MGPS, 6000"]}]}
